那么, 孩子们, 你们想听\n我变聋的那个故事吗?
So,kids,would you like to hear the story of the time I went deaf?
他干嘛问我们?
Why does he even ask?
是啊, 无论如何他\n都会讲给我们听
I know,he's just going to tell us anyway.
我确实会讲
I sure am.
故事的开始\n是Robin来到酒吧说……
It all began when robin strolled into the bar and said...
说你是我的小贱人
say you're my bitch.
我是你的小贱人\n这次是为什么?
I'm your bitch. Why this time?
因为今晚\n我将把大家全带进Okay
Cause tonight I'm getting us all into okay.
"Okay" 太棒了!
"Okay," awesome!
怎么回事? 我刚才中风了吗?
What's going on? Did I just have a stroke?
Okay是一个夜总会的名字
Okay is the name of a club.
对, 这有点让人难以置信
Yeah,it's supposed to be incredibly exclusive.
有一次我和朋友在外面\n等了两个小时, 还是进不去
This friend of mine once waited outside for two hours,couldn't get in.
你的朋友叫"你"?
A friend of yours named you?
不, 我的朋友叫"闭嘴"
No,a friend of mine named shut up.
好吧, 夜总会的老板\n和我去同一个健身馆
Yeah,well,the owner goes to my gym.
结果发现他是我播报的\n都市新闻的忠实观众
It turns out that he is a fan of my reporting for metro news one.
所以我在今晚出席的名单上
So now I'm on the list for tonight.
干的不错, Sherbotsky
Nice going,sherbotsky.
你又长又难拼的名字\n变得家喻户晓了
You're becoming a long and difficult-to-spell household name.
他甚至把我列入了V.I.P. 房的名单
He's even getting me into the V.I.P. Room.
对, 他只是想让你看看他的V.I.P. \n如果你知道我在说什么
Yeah,he just wants to show you his own V.I.P.,If you know what I mean.
好吧, 在你的小世界里V.I.P. 代表什么?
All right,what does V.I.P. Stand for in your little universe?
嗯, 我知道"p"表示阴茎
Well,I know that "p" is penis.
好吧, 你们两个会跟我一起去\n我应该邀请Marshal和Lily吗?
Great,so you guys are in. Should I invite marshal and lily?
有什么好笑的呢?
Why was this funny?
我来解释给你们听
I'll explain.
你们知道, Lily是幼儿园老师
You see,lily was a kindergarten teacher,
命中注定的一次午休时间时……
and so one fateful nap time...
Austin和我在\n迷人的小床上共渡周末
austin and I spent saturday night at the most charming little bed and breakfast.
那太美妙了
It was so nice.
这个周末你怎么过的?
What did you do this weekend?
来吧, 加油, 咕嘟, 咕嘟, 咕嘟!
Go,come on,chug,chug,chug!
十秒!
Ten conds!
喝干了, 输家!
Suck it,losers!
你知道, 与未婚夫普通平静的日子
you know,quiet time with the fiance
我也不知道, 我就觉得丢脸
I don't know,I just felt embarrassed.
Claire和我同年，她和丈夫享受着\n所有成年人做的上等的事情
Claire is my age and she and her husband do all this classy grownup stuff.
也许我们也应该开始做些成熟的事
Maybe we should start doing some grownup stuff.
我们早上做的不就是吗
That's some pretty grownup stuff we did this morning.
对啊, 但不是上等的
Yeah,but it wasn't classy.
也许我们该办个品酒会
Maybe we should have a wine-tasting party.
我喜欢酒 我也喜欢品尝
I like wine. I like tasting.
你知道我能狂欢\n来狂欢吧 来摇摆吧 成人风格
You know I can party. Let's do it. Let's rock it. Maturity style.
以后她就会鼓动\n他参加读书俱乐部, 烹饪班……
And ever since then she's been signing him up for book clubs,cooking classes...
所有能把下月千元工资花掉的事情
all the things you do when you know where your next thousand lays are coming from
所以, 不, Lily和Marshal\nl不会和我们一起去
so,no,lily andarshall will not be joining us.
知道了 不管怎样\nTed, 我要说的第二件事
Got it. Anyway,ted,part two of my story:
我朋友kelly也会去
My friend kelly's going to be there.
Kelly, 看样子我要爱上她？
Kelly,who supposedly I'm going to love.
噢, 你会喜欢上Kelly的
Oh,you are going to love kelly.
她很风趣, 很聪明, 她单身……
She's fun,she's smart,she lives in the moment...
翻译: 她很丑, 她很丑\n她是丑人中的丑人
translation: She's ugly,she's ugly,she ugs in the ugly.
噢, 还有她很正点
Oh,and she's totally hot.
好吧, 我猜今晚我可以接手她
Okay,I guess I could take her off your hands for an evening.
那你还有别的正点，单身的朋友吗?
so do you have any other hot,single friends?
没有 Kelly……
No. Kelly...
噢, 天那, Ted, 你的运动衫!
oh,no,ted,your blazer!
怎么, 怎么, 怎么?
What,what,what?
有人弄的如此耀眼
Somebody spilled gorgeous all over it.
--不错\n--谢谢
--Love it. \n--Thank you.
瞧他完美的发型
And his hair was perfect.
我们穿了一样的衬衫
We're wearing the same shirt.
噢, 等等, 不, 是\n我的衬衫反射在你的上了
Oh,wait,no,that's just my shirt reflected in yours.
女孩们和鱼的24条相同点之一是
One of the 24 similarities between girls and fish is that
他们都被发光的物体吸引
they're both attracted to shiny objects.
你从来没看过我的博客, 是不?
You really never read my blog,do you?
好吧, 罐头小子, 我们狂欢去吧
All right,tin man,let's hit it.
好吧, 嗯\n好好享受你们的迪斯科, 伙计们
All right,well,have fun at your little disco,guys.
你们两到底怎么了?
What the hell happened to these two?
我和Marshall长大了
Marshall and I are just growing up.
对, 这会变的很不错
Yeah,it's going to be sweet,too.
就象今晚, 我们将品尝所有这些不同的酒
Like tonight,we're tasting all these different wines,
与这些美味的奶酪组合起来
pairing them up with these cool gourmet cheeses.
哇, 谁能料到忠于一段异性恋情
Wow,who knew being in a committed heterosexual retionship
……可以让一个男人\n变得这么像同性恋？
could make a guy so gay?
好吧, 酷小孩们要走了
All right,cool kids are leaving now.
爷爷, 奶奶, 不用等我们了
Grandma,grandpa,don't wait up
天那, 噢, 我的天那\n今晚这里有好多辣妹啊
my,oh,my. There are some ferocious-looking cutlets here tonight.
好吧, 勾引计划专栏, 找个辣妹
All right,hookup strategy. Colon,find a cutlet,
早早锁定住她
lock her in early,
整晚纠缠她直到她属于我
grind with her all nightill she's mine.
你这些计划起过作用吗?
Do these strategies ever work for you?
应该这样问\n这些计划什么时候没起作用?
The question is: Do these strategies ever not work for me?
两个问题, 答案都是一半一半
Either way,the answer is about half the time.
我的小贱人们! 瞧我的\n呃,他们是和我一起的
My bitches! Check this out um,they're with me.
呃, 我们也是她的小贱人
Um,we're her bitches,too.
我们还是在这等着
Wel wait here.
依据现在的利率情况
And with today's interest rate climate,
你得去申请30年的低压贷款
you've got to go for the 30-year fixed mortgage.
--噢, 是啊\n--对
--Oh,totally. \n--Yeah.
嗯, Marshall, 说说你们的事吧?
So,marshall,what about you?
你们在考虑买房生小孩吗?
You guys thinking house,baby?
噢! 不, 我们会等等\n再考虑生孩子的事
Oh! No,think we're going to wait on the baby thing.
我是说, 我喜欢小孩\n小孩很可爱
I mean,I love babies. Babies rule.
小胖胳膊还有……
Pudgy arms and stuff...
但是, 呃, 他们让你显老
but,uh,they make you old.
就像把你困在原地\n的大铁锚……
Kind of like this anchor weighing you down to one spot...
永远困住
forever.
我怀孕3个月了
I'm three months pregnant.
别觉得尴尬, 伙计们
Not awkward,guys.
别尴尬除非\n我们让事情变的尴尬
Not awkward unless we let it be awkward.
这地方看起来不错\nkelly在这吗?
This place seems great. Is kelly here?
对, 她就在这
Yeah,she's around somewhere.
呃, 我们去找她吧\n我会介绍你们认识
Uh,let's go find her. I'll introduce you guys.
然后我就得去V.I.P. 房了
Then I should probably duck into the V.I.P. Room.
这很蠢而且专制, 不是吗?
It's so stupid and arbitrary,isn't it?
谁可以去V.I.P房谁不能?
Who gets to be a V.I.P and who doesn't?
我们能去吗?
Can we come?
也不是那么专制
It's not that arbitrary.
-哇, 这地方真吵\n-你觉得吗?
Whoa,this place is loud. You think?
好吧, 是有点吵
Ok,it is a little loud
Kelly在那边!
There is Kelly
你想去找个能讲话的地方吗?
You want to go somewhere we can talk
好啊!
Totally!
……好吧……
......Okay......
不觉得Ted没有\n邀我和他一起出去很奇怪吗?
think it was kind of weird that ted didn't invite me out with him?
为什么? 你宁愿去某个夜总会\n充满噪音和汗臭味, 还有……
Why? You'd rather be out at some dance club,all noisy and sweaty,with the...
这就是你想要的吗?
is that what you want?
is this what you want?
30年的低押借款……
"30-year fixed mortgage...
我怀孕3个月了
I'm three months pregnant."
这是该尴尬的时候了
That was awkward.
我们开始品酒吧!
Let's start drinking!
别这么急\n要让红酒的单宁酸醇香
Not so fast. In order for the tannins to mellow,
我们应该让它先“呼吸”30分钟
we should let it breathe for about 30 minutes.
该死的单宁酸
Freaking tannins.
那么, 你怎么认识Robin的?
So,how do you know Robin?
人马座!
Sagittarius
离威郡很近吗?
Is that near Westchester?
我很乐意来一杯!
I would love one!
一瓶啤酒就好了!
Just a beer!
你知道他们现在在干嘛吗?
do you know what they're doing in there right now?
他们在看Claire的超声波录象带
They're watching claire's ultrasound video.
我发誓, 连婴儿自己\n都觉得无聊了
And I swear to god,even the baby looks bored.
拜托, 没那么糟糕
Come on,it's not that bad.
我们已经开始溶入这些人了
We're really starting to click with these guys.
Claire和Austin刚刚还邀请我们\n去参加周六晚的奶酪火锅宴
Claire and austin just invited us to their fondue fest next saturday night.
你是真的想让我\n对奶酪火锅感到兴奋吗?
Are you honestly trying to get me excited about fondue?
把食物浸在热奶酪里\n有什么不让人喜欢的?
It's dipping stuff in hot cheese. What's not to love?
好吧, 听起来是不错
Okay,that does sound good.
但是是与一群乏味的家伙\n把食物浸在热奶酪里
But it's dipping stuff in hot cheese with boring people.
Marshall, 我们是时候成熟起来了
Marshall,it's time for us to grow up.
Marshall知道她是对的
Marshall knew she was right.
他必须别再表现的象个小孩
He had to stop acting like a kid.
但不是今晚
But not tonight.
好吧, 我们的公寓在3楼
Now,our apartment was on the third floor,
所以不确定这部分是不是真的
so I'm not sure if this part is actually true,
但是Marshall叔叔发誓\n这是真正有发生的
but uncle marshall swears it happened.
记程车!
Taxi!
新专辑很棒 平静优美
the new album is great. It's all smooth and polished,
不象以前的那些音乐一样\n那么节奏很强了
not dark a heavy like the early stuff.
噢, 是啊, Nora Jones越来越棒了
Oh,yeah,nora jones just gets better and better.
天那, 告诉我现在能开始品酒了
Please,tell me we can drink the wine now.
再等5分钟, 别弄糟单宁酸
Five more minutes.Don't want to rush those tannins.
该死的单宁酸
Freaking tannins.
你真喜欢这地方吗?
You really like this place?
你不知道我在说什么, 是吗?
You have no idea what I am saying,do you?
我是从外星球来的!
I am from outer space!
我因为上了一只海豚\n被赶出海底世界!
I got thrown out of Sea World for humping a dolphin!
我尿裤子了!
I am wetting my pants!
我就在那时候意识到
I think that's when I realized,
夜总会不是那么棒
clubs weren't awesome.
夜总会一点都不好
Clubs weren't even okay.
夜总会太烂了
Clubs sucked.
我得离开这
I had to get out of there.
--嘿, Robin\n--嘿
--Hey,robin. \n--Hey.
--你怎么不在里面?\n--我在给那老板打电话
--Why aren't you inside? \n--I'm calling the owner.
里面那家伙不让我进V.I.P. 房
There's a guy in there who won't let me in to the stupid V.I.P. Room.
你在这干嘛?
What are you doing here?
噢, 我有这个心情\n所以就来这狂欢了
Oh,I had this move,so I came here to bust it.
你能把我弄进去吗?
Can you get me in?
好样的 语音信箱
Great. Voice mail.
--谢谢, 一会见!\n--拜!
--Thanks,I'll see you! \n--Bye!
噢, 天那, 他才刚刚到这
Oh,come on,he just got here.
他肯定很有名
He's probably famous.
噢, 是啊 Affleck有3兄弟吗?
Oh,yeah. Isn't there a third affleck brother?
Keith Affleck还是\nBrian Affleck还是其他什么人?
Keith affleck or brian affleck or something?
天啊, 我们刚刚\n看见了Brian Affleck
Holy crap,we just saw brian affleck.
不是我有多在意能进V.I.P. 房
It's not like I care so much about getting in the V.I.P. Room,
我已经去过无数个V.I.P. 房
I have been in tons of V.I.P. Rooms.
我不是第一次进V.I.P. 房
I'm not exactly a V.I.P. Room virgin.
但是真的, 回我电话
But seriously,call me back.
噢, 呃, 我刚刚还在里面
Oh,um,I was just in there,
Robin Sherbotsky 我在单子上
robin sherbotsky. I'm on the list.
名字已经被划掉了 抱歉
Name's already crossed off. Sorry.
但是我是Robin Sherbotsky
But I'm robin sherbotsky.
我是一台的记者
I'm a reporter for channel one.
有一台吗? 到后面去排队
There's a channel one? Back of the line.
应该跟着Brian Affleck溜进去
Should have snuck in with brian affleck.
我要走了, 回头见
I am bailing,see ya.
噢, 嘿, 我看不见她的脸\n她辣吗?
Oh hey,I can not see her face.Is she hot?
嗨
Hi
迷人的眼睛
Nice eyes
笑的很可爱
Cute smile
你泡不到的
Out of your league
啊! 外套寄存女佣\n别让这家伙取走外套!
Aah! Coat wench,do not uncheck that man's jacket!
抱歉, 只是在演戏
Sorry,just being dramatic.
你不是外套寄存女佣
You're not a coat wench.
不, 不, 不, 外套寄存女佣\n我喜欢这个
No,no,no,coat wench,I like it.
我需要一个称号
I should get a sign made up.
你在这干嘛? Lily让你走吗?
What are you doing here? Lily let you go?
Lily? 谁管她, 是不?
Lily? Who cares,right?
--你完了\n--噢, 我是完了.
--You are so dead. \n--Oh,I am so dead.
哇, 我要回家了
Wow,I'm going home.
别, 呃 我把我的屁股很有可能还有\n我身体的其他部分拿来冒险
No,uh-uh. I put my ass and probably other parts of my body on the line
来这和我的兄弟狂欢
to come down here and party with my bro.
现在, 管他妈的我们去派对吧
Now,damn it we're going to party.
--好吧, 一瓶啤酒\n--好!
--All right,one beer. \n--Yes!
太好了, 我终于不需要\n等半个小时才能喝酒了
Finally,I don't have to wait a half an hour for a drink.
半小时后
ONE HALF HOUR LETER...
耶!
Yeah!
没有单宁酸!
No tannins!
噢, 天那, 我不敢相信\n我差点忘记告诉你们这个了
Oh,man,Ican't believe I forgot to tell you this.
这是故事里很重要的一部分
This is important to the story.
那天早些时候
Earlier that day,
Marshall去牙医那\n装了个临时的假齿冠
marshall went to the dentist and got a temporary crown put in.
嗯, 所以无论如何……
Okay,so anyway...
来吧, 我们走!
Come on,Let's go!
我要留下来!
I'm staying1
Marshall, 你还好吧?
Marshall,are you okay?
又一次, 我当时不在那
Again,I wasn't there,
所以在细节上我有点模糊
so I'm a little foggy on the details.
记程车!
Taxi!
--嘿\n--嘿
--Hey. \n--Hey.
Marshall刚刚从我们的派对上溜了
Marshall just ditched out on our own party.
你能让我进去吗? 我要杀了他
Can you get me in there? I kind of need to kill him.
事实上, 我自己都进不去了
Actually,I can't even get myself in.
我真是个呆子
I was such a dork.
我被认出来了一次\n就觉得自己是Julia Roberts
I get recognized one time,and I start thinking I'm julia roberts.
我不是什么V.I.P.
I'm no V.I.P.
我连I.P. 都不是
I'm not even an I.P.
我只是颗平凡的小小P
I'm just a lowly little pea,
坐在街边台阶上
sitting out here in the gutter.
你知道吗?
You know something?
我永远把台阶上的小P\n看的比Julia Roberts重
I'd take a pea in the gutter over julia roberts
Barney在那边，我要走了！
There's Barney,I'm leaving1
我弄伤牙齿了!
I broke my tooth!
你有……
Do you have... ...
阿司匹林?
any aspirin?
也许那里有……
Maybe there's...
一台机器……
a machine in... ...
在卫生间
the restroom.
那天
Now to this day,
我不知道在那发生了什么事
I don't know what happened in there,
但是几分钟后\n当Marshall出来的时候……
but when marshall came out a few minutes later...
--糟糕的一晚?\n--是啊
--rough night? \n--Yeah.
这种夜总会应该很有趣, 不是吗?
These clubs are supposed to be fun,right?
为什么我这么讨厌这些呢?
Why do I hate them so much?
因为所有这些\n你本该喜欢上的……
Because all of the stuff you're supposed to like..
通常都很糟糕
usually sucks.
就象这些夜总会……或者巡航
Like these clubs...or cruises.
或者除夕夜
Or new year's eve.
--或者超级杯比赛（美国最大的橄榄球比赛）\n--或者游行
--Or the super bowl. \n--Or parades.
--火箭\n--或者游行
--The rockettes. \n--Or parades.
--你已经说过这个了\n--我真的很讨厌游行
--You said that already. \n--I really hate parades.
好吧
Okay.
他刚刚从我们的派对中溜走了!
He just left in the middle of our own party!
你不会这样做
You don't do that.
除非, 当然你在追\n某个已经这么做了的人, 那么……
Unless,of course,you're chasing after somebody who's already done it,and then...
那么我不会觉得有什么
then I think it's okay.
嗯, 我不想站在他那边\n但是拜托, 品酒会?
Well,I hate to take his side,but come on,a wine tasting?
下周六有什么大计划\n拼字游戏之夜?
What's the big plan for next Saturday,scrale night?
别去看你的邮箱
Don't check your e-mail.
你为什么要变成这类人呢?
Why are you becoming this person?
我听说你在大学时\n大胆的激怒了校园巡视队
I heard that in college you flashed a campus tour group on a dare.
有一次是因为比胆量\n另外一次是为了好玩
Once on a dare. The other times were just for fun.
我不再是大学生了
I'm not in college anymore.
我很想回到那时候\n做我原来的样子, 但是……
I'd love to go back and be that person again,but..
你不能让时间倒退\n只能一直向前走
you can't move backwards. You can only go foreword.
呃, 不对, 你能到任何地方\n只要你想去
Um,false. You can go wherever you want.
我想问题是, 你想去哪?
I guess the question is,where do you want to go?
我想进这个夜总会\n找到我的未婚夫
I want to go into this club and find my fiance.
嗯, 这个办不到
Well,that you can't do.
要赌一下吗?
Want to bet?
跟着我做
Follow my lead.
嘿, 大块头
Hey,big guy.
我说跟着我做
I said follow my lead.
拜托, 拜托 跟着她做
Please,please. Follow her lead.
来吧, 快点
Come on. Do it,please.
跟着她, 拜托 对, 快点
Follow her,please. Yes,please.
这是我见过最好的\n也是唯一见过的四个乳房
those were the four greatest and only breasts I've ever seen.
嗯, 是啊, 如果每个人都\n不停的告诉你什么应该是有趣的
Yeah,see,if everyone keeps telling you something is supposed to be fun,
--通常都不是那么有趣\n--对! 对啊
--it's usually not. \n--Right! Right.
那么, 按照这个逻辑\n如果我们说, 出去约会……
So,by that logic,if you and I were to say,go out on a date...
嗯, 那我们就不可能去\n任何好玩的地方
well,then we couldn't go anywhere that's supposed to be fun.
是啊 正是如此
Right. The dmv it is.
那么我们一起去洗牙吧
Then we'll get our teeth cleaned.
--听起来很糟糕 这是个约会\n--好吧!
--Sounds awful. It's a date. \n--Okay!
还有一个大问题需要解决
But there's still one big question that needs to be answered.
你认为这些外套\n我一次能穿上多少件?
How many of these coats do you think I can put on all at once?
好吧, 走四步……
okay,for the wedge...
Barney?\nBarney?
Ted. 拿好你的外套 我们要走了
Ted. Get your coat. We're leaving.
什么…… 发生什么了, 呃……
What... what happened to that,um...
你纠缠的那个辣妹?
cutlet you were grinding with?
--那是我的堂妹Leslie\n--什么?!
--That was my cousin leslie. \n--What?!
不, 不, 不 你不会取笑我, Ted
No,no,no. We're not laughing about this,ted.
这不会成为我们接下来\n几个月里不停谈论的笑话
This is not gonna be some funny story that we'll be telling in a couple months.
这不会变的象
It's not gonna be like,
"嘿, 哈, 记得那次你和……" \n不！！！
"hey,ha,remember that time when you were grinding with..." no.
你知道为什么吗?
And you know why?
因为…… 斜体字…… \n今晚什么事也没有
Because...italics... this night did not happen.
你保证你永远永远
You promise me you will never,ever,
永远不会告诉另外一个\n活着的人今晚发生了什么
ever tell another living soul what transpired here tonight.
你保证
You promise.
--好吧\n--我保证
--All right. \n--Promise.
好吧, 我保证\n我们找到Marshall然后走, 好吗?
All right,I promise. Get marshall and go,okay?
嘿, 谢谢你救了我一晚
Hey,thanks for saving my night.
我很快会找你
I'll talk to you soo yeah.
呃, 嘿, 小费, Barney
Um,hey,tiper,barney.
为什么? 我没有寄存外套
Why? I didn't check a coat.
就算我寄存了\n原则上来说, 小费……
And even if I did,on principle,tip jars have become so...
笑话: Barney\n与一个女孩纠缠整晚……
funny story: Barney was grinding with this girl all night...
好吧!
fine!
我学了个新把戏
I'm handing a new trick.
就那样, Marshall和Lily\n重新发现了他们的青春
So,marshall and lily rediscovered their youth.
那很不错
It was nice.
后来他们…… 甜的发腻
And then it got... icky.
我们高兴你们今晚来了
I'm really glad you guys came out tonight.
你知道, 兄弟, 我能说几句吗?
You know,dude,can I just say something?
你们出来没邀请让我有点伤心
It kind of hurt that you guys didn't invite me out.
我是说, 我知道自从我订婚后\n情形有些变化
I mean,I know things have changed since I got engaged,
但是被邀请的感觉会很好!
but it would have been nice to be asked!
我真抱歉!
I'm sorry!
--我只是以为……\n--他们今晚放的歌不错!
--I just assumed... \n--they played some good songs tonight!
--我是说, 以后……\n--我知道, 我知道
--I mean,lately... \n--I know,I know.
这就象我们突然变成\n两个世界的人了
It just seems like suddenly we're living in two different worlds.
也许你和Barney有更多共同语言
Maybe you've got more in common with barney.
什么?
What?
你疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
你认为我喜欢去这总夜总会吗?
You think I like going to those clubs?
我宁愿去你的品酒会
I'd so much rather go to your fruity little wine tasting.
噢, 天那, 我要吐了
Oh,god,I'm gonna barf.
我的包呢? 我的包呢? 我没事
Where's my purse? Where's my purse? I'm okay.
问题是
The problem is,
除非有人能和你在一起\n你做不了那些夫妻做的事情
you can't do any of that couple stuff unless you have someone to do it with,
而我要找个伴儿的话
and the only way I'm gonna find that
只能和Barney去做些单身傻事
someone is by going out and doing stupid single stuff with barney.
什么?
What?
但是,伙计
But,man,
我找到另一半时
when I find her,
我们也去办个像样的品酒会
we're gonna have some bad-ass wine tastings.
就这么定了
It's a plan.
嘿, 可能就是那个\n寄存外套的可爱女孩
Hey,maybe it'll be that cute coat check girl.
对! 可能真会是她
Yeah! Maybe it will be.
不是
It wasn'T.
你知道, Ted
You know,ted,
我不想说什么那时候快到了
I don't say this nearly enough,
--但是我真的……\n--那地方有很棒的色拉!
--but I really...\n--that place has great salads!